{"classes":["DATE","DAY","MONEY","GPE","CURRENCY","ORG","PERCENT","PERSON"],"annotations":[["Forex traders said the rupee lost momentum as worries over the looming 25% U.S. tariff on Indian goods, set to take effect from August 27, drove strong dollar demand from importers.\r\n\r\nThe rupee depreciated 22 paise to 87.78 against the U.S. dollar in early trade on Tuesday (August 26, 2025) after the U.S. issued a draft notice detailing plans to impose an additional 25% tariff on India.\r\n\r\nForex traders said the rupee lost momentum as worries over the looming 25% U.S. tariff on Indian goods, set to take effect from August 27, drove strong dollar demand from importers.\r\n\r\nThe United States has issued a draft notice detailing plans to implement the additional 25% tariff on Indian products, as previously announced by President Donald Trump.\r\n\r\nAt the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 87.74 against the U.S. dollar, then fell to 87.78, registering a decline of 22 paise over its previous close.\r\n\r\nIn the initial trade, the rupee touched an early high of 87.69 against the greenback.\r\n\r\nOn Monday, the rupee pared initial gains to settle 4 paise lower at 87.56 against the U.S. dollar.\r\n",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"],[23,28,"CURRENCY"],[71,74,"CURRENCY"],[75,79,"GPE"],[104,137,"DATE"],[152,158,"CURRENCY"],[189,194,"CURRENCY"],[207,224,"MONEY"],[237,241,"GPE"],[242,251,"CURRENCY"],[267,274,"DAY"],[276,291,"DATE"],[303,307,"GPE"],[370,373,"PERCENT"],[384,390,"GPE"],[417,422,"CURRENCY"],[465,467,"PERCENT"],[469,473,"GPE"],[522,531,"DATE"],[546,552,"CURRENCY"],[583,596,"GPE"],[667,670,"PERCENT"],[725,748,"PERSON"],[798,803,"CURRENCY"],[814,819,"MONEY"],[832,843,"CURRENCY"],[858,863,"MONEY"],[890,898,"MONEY"],[953,958,"CURRENCY"],[984,989,"MONEY"],[1019,1025,"DAY"],[1031,1036,"CURRENCY"],[1067,1074,"MONEY"],[1084,1089,"MONEY"],[1102,1106,"GPE"],[1107,1113,"CURRENCY"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["The rupee depreciated 22 paise to 87.78 against the U.S. dollar in early trade on Tuesday (August 26, 2025) after the U.S. issued a draft notice detailing plans to impose an additional 25% tariff on India.\r",{"entities":[[4,9,"CURRENCY"],[22,30,"MONEY"],[34,39,"MONEY"],[52,56,"GPE"],[57,63,"CURRENCY"],[82,89,"DAY"],[91,106,"DATE"],[118,122,"GPE"],[185,187,"PERCENT"],[199,204,"GPE"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["Forex traders said the rupee lost momentum as worries over the looming 25% U.S. tariff on Indian goods, set to take effect from August 27, drove strong dollar demand from importers.\r",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"],[23,28,"CURRENCY"],[71,74,"PERCENT"],[75,79,"GPE"],[128,137,"DATE"],[152,158,"CURRENCY"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["The United States has issued a draft notice detailing plans to implement the additional 25% tariff on Indian products, as previously announced by President Donald Trump.\r",{"entities":[[4,17,"GPE"],[88,91,"PERCENT"],[146,168,"PERSON"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["At the interbank foreign exchange market, the rupee opened at 87.74 against the U.S. dollar, then fell to 87.78, registering a decline of 22 paise over its previous close.\r",{"entities":[[46,51,"CURRENCY"],[62,67,"MONEY"],[80,84,"GPE"],[85,91,"CURRENCY"],[106,111,"MONEY"],[138,146,"MONEY"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["In the initial trade, the rupee touched an early high of 87.69 against the greenback.\r",{"entities":[[26,31,"CURRENCY"],[57,62,"MONEY"]]}],["\r",{"entities":[]}],["On Monday, the rupee pared initial gains to settle 4 paise lower at 87.56 against the U.S. dollar.\r",{"entities":[[3,9,"DAY"],[15,20,"CURRENCY"],[51,58,"MONEY"],[68,73,"MONEY"],[86,90,"GPE"],[91,97,"CURRENCY"]]}],["",{"entities":[]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}