{"classes":["ORG","DATE","NAMES","LOC","OCC"],"annotations":[["On September 10, 2023, Anita Sharma, a journalist with The Times of India, reported from New Delhi about a major conference organized by the United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) in partnership with Harvard University. The conference was attended by Dr. Michael Roberts, a professor of economics at London School of Economics, and Suresh Iyer, the Managing Director of Reliance Industries Limited. Earlier that week, on September 7, 2023, Prime Minister Raghav Verma of India met with CEO Emily Zhang of Tesla Inc. in Mumbai to discuss renewable energy investments. During the same month, Professor Kavita Nair from IIT Bombay presented her team’s research in San Francisco, California, at a summit hosted by the World Economic Forum, where several data scientists and policy analysts shared insights on sustainable technology.",{"entities":[[59,73,"ORG"],[141,184,"ORG"],[205,224,"ORG"],[305,331,"ORG"],[375,383,"ORG"],[510,515,"ORG"],[622,625,"ORG"],[719,739,"ORG"]]}],["On September 10, 2023, Anita Sharma, a journalist with The Times of India, reported from New Delhi about a major conference organized by the United Nations Development Programme (UNDP) in partnership with Harvard University. The conference was attended by Dr. Michael Roberts, a professor of economics at London School of Economics, and Suresh Iyer, the Managing Director of Reliance Industries Limited. Earlier that week, on September 7, 2023, Prime Minister Raghav Verma of India met with CEO Emily Zhang of Tesla Inc. in Mumbai to discuss renewable energy investments. During the same month, Professor Kavita Nair from IIT Bombay presented her team’s research in San Francisco, California, at a summit hosted by the World Economic Forum, where several data scientists and policy analysts shared insights on sustainable technology.",{"entities":[[3,21,"DATE"],[23,35,"NAMES"],[39,49,"OCC"],[59,73,"ORG"],[89,98,"LOC"],[141,184,"ORG"],[205,224,"ORG"],[256,275,"NAMES"],[279,288,"OCC"],[305,331,"ORG"],[337,348,"NAMES"],[354,371,"OCC"],[375,383,"ORG"],[426,443,"DATE"],[445,459,"OCC"],[460,472,"NAMES"],[491,494,"OCC"],[495,506,"NAMES"],[510,515,"ORG"],[524,530,"LOC"],[595,604,"OCC"],[605,616,"NAMES"],[622,632,"ORG"],[666,679,"LOC"],[681,691,"LOC"],[719,739,"ORG"],[755,770,"OCC"],[775,790,"OCC"]]}]]}