{"classes":["ORG","DATE","NAMES","LOC","OCC"],"annotations":[["On January 10, 2022, Dr. Vikram Sethi, Chief Data Scientist at National Stock Exchange of India, addressed a gathering in New Delhi to discuss the impact of predictive analytics on capital markets. Alongside him, Maria Gonzalez, Senior Economist at the World Bank, explained how developing nations could leverage data-driven strategies to achieve inclusive growth. The panel was moderated by Professor Alan Wright of London School of Economics, who highlighted case studies from the United Kingdom and Germany. During the same conference, Amitabh Rao, Director of Technology at Infosys Limited, presented a prototype of a machine learning system designed for fraud detection.\r\n\r\nOn February 2, 2022, Naomi Tan, Policy Advisor at the Asian Development Bank, visited Singapore to meet with Hiroshi Yamamoto, Governor of the Bank of Japan. They reviewed monetary policies adopted during the pandemic and their effect on regional trade. The session also included remarks from Dr. Claire Dubois, a financial historian at Sorbonne University in Paris, who traced the evolution of regulatory frameworks since the 1980s. That evening, Rahul Verma, Chief Legal Officer at ICICI Bank, hosted a dinner with representatives from Goldman Sachs and JPMorgan Chase, discussing cross-border compliance issues.\r\n\r\nOn March 18, 2022, in New York City, Emily Thompson, Editor-in-Chief of The Wall Street Journal, interviewed Satya Nadella, Chief Executive Officer of Microsoft Corporation, about cloud adoption in global financial systems. The event also featured Dr. Kavya Narayan, a blockchain researcher at Massachusetts Institute of Technology, who spoke about decentralized finance. Meanwhile, in Bengaluru, Arjun Menon, Head of Innovation at Tata Consultancy Services, unveiled a pilot project using AI to automate loan approvals.\r\n\r\nBy April 5, 2022, Olivia Chen, Senior Investment Manager at Temasek Holdings, organized a seminar in Hong Kong, inviting David Miller, Managing Director at BlackRock, and Ananya Sharma, Head of Equity Research at Kotak Mahindra Bank. Their discussion revolved around the rise of environmental, social, and governance (ESG) funds. The keynote was delivered by Dr. Hassan Ali, an energy economist from King Saud University, who emphasized the role of sustainable financing in the Middle East.\r\n\r\nOn May 12, 2022, Jason Reed, Technology Correspondent for BBC News, published a report from San Francisco, covering the annual conference of Tesla Inc. At the event, Elon Musk, Chief Executive Officer of Tesla, introduced innovations in autonomous driving, while Dr. Sophia Keller, a robotics engineer at ETH Zurich, discussed AI-driven safety mechanisms. In parallel, Mehul Choudhary, Policy Head at the Reserve Bank of India, issued a statement from Mumbai, addressing the regulatory approach toward cryptocurrency adoption.\r\n\r\nLater, on June 25, 2022, Professor William Harris of Harvard Business School convened a workshop in Boston with participants including Sarah Ahmed, Chief Risk Officer at Deutsche Bank, and Carlos Fernandez, Compliance Director at Banco Santander. They debated the role of ethics in machine learning algorithms applied to financial credit scoring. Concluding the event, Nidhi Kapoor, Lead Researcher at United Nations Economic and Social Council, released a paper outlining global standards for responsible AI deployment in the finance sector.",{"entities":[[3,19,"DATE"],[21,37,"NAMES"],[63,95,"ORG"],[122,131,"LOC"],[213,227,"NAMES"],[253,263,"ORG"],[402,413,"NAMES"],[417,443,"ORG"],[483,497,"LOC"],[502,510,"LOC"],[539,550,"NAMES"],[578,593,"ORG"],[682,698,"DATE"],[700,709,"NAMES"],[733,755,"ORG"],[765,774,"LOC"],[788,804,"NAMES"],[822,836,"ORG"],[972,989,"NAMES"],[1016,1035,"ORG"],[1039,1044,"LOC"],[1106,1112,"DATE"],[1127,1138,"NAMES"],[1163,1173,"ORG"],[1217,1230,"ORG"],[1235,1249,"ORG"],[1300,1314,"DATE"],[1319,1332,"LOC"],[1334,1348,"NAMES"],[1369,1392,"ORG"],[1406,1419,"NAMES"],[1448,1469,"ORG"],[1545,1562,"NAMES"],[1591,1628,"ORG"],[1683,1692,"LOC"],[1694,1705,"NAMES"],[1729,1754,"ORG"],[1824,1837,"DATE"],[1839,1850,"NAMES"],[1881,1897,"ORG"],[1922,1931,"LOC"],[1942,1954,"NAMES"],[1977,1986,"ORG"],[1992,2005,"NAMES"],[2034,2054,"ORG"],[2180,2194,"NAMES"],[2221,2241,"ORG"],[2299,2311,"LOC"],[2318,2330,"DATE"],[2332,2342,"NAMES"],[2373,2381,"ORG"],[2407,2420,"LOC"],[2456,2466,"ORG"],[2481,2490,"NAMES"],[2519,2524,"ORG"],[2578,2595,"NAMES"],[2620,2630,"ORG"],[2684,2699,"NAMES"],[2720,2741,"ORG"],[2767,2773,"LOC"],[2855,2868,"DATE"],[2880,2894,"NAMES"],[2898,2921,"ORG"],[2945,2951,"LOC"],[2980,2991,"NAMES"],[3015,3028,"ORG"],[3034,3050,"NAMES"],[3075,3091,"ORG"],[3214,3226,"NAMES"],[3247,3289,"ORG"]]}],["On January 10, 2022, Dr. Vikram Sethi, Chief Data Scientist at National Stock Exchange of India, addressed a gathering in New Delhi to discuss the impact of predictive analytics on capital markets. Alongside him, Maria Gonzalez, Senior Economist at the World Bank, explained how developing nations could leverage data-driven strategies to achieve inclusive growth. The panel was moderated by Professor Alan Wright of London School of Economics, who highlighted case studies from the United Kingdom and Germany. During the same conference, Amitabh Rao, Director of Technology at Infosys Limited, presented a prototype of a machine learning system designed for fraud detection.\r\n\r\nOn February 2, 2022, Naomi Tan, Policy Advisor at the Asian Development Bank, visited Singapore to meet with Hiroshi Yamamoto, Governor of the Bank of Japan. They reviewed monetary policies adopted during the pandemic and their effect on regional trade. The session also included remarks from Dr. Claire Dubois, a financial historian at Sorbonne University in Paris, who traced the evolution of regulatory frameworks since the 1980s. That evening, Rahul Verma, Chief Legal Officer at ICICI Bank, hosted a dinner with representatives from Goldman Sachs and JPMorgan Chase, discussing cross-border compliance issues.\r\n\r\nOn March 18, 2022, in New York City, Emily Thompson, Editor-in-Chief of The Wall Street Journal, interviewed Satya Nadella, Chief Executive Officer of Microsoft Corporation, about cloud adoption in global financial systems. The event also featured Dr. Kavya Narayan, a blockchain researcher at Massachusetts Institute of Technology, who spoke about decentralized finance. Meanwhile, in Bengaluru, Arjun Menon, Head of Innovation at Tata Consultancy Services, unveiled a pilot project using AI to automate loan approvals.\r\n\r\nBy April 5, 2022, Olivia Chen, Senior Investment Manager at Temasek Holdings, organized a seminar in Hong Kong, inviting David Miller, Managing Director at BlackRock, and Ananya Sharma, Head of Equity Research at Kotak Mahindra Bank. Their discussion revolved around the rise of environmental, social, and governance (ESG) funds. The keynote was delivered by Dr. Hassan Ali, an energy economist from King Saud University, who emphasized the role of sustainable financing in the Middle East.\r\n\r\nOn May 12, 2022, Jason Reed, Technology Correspondent for BBC News, published a report from San Francisco, covering the annual conference of Tesla Inc. At the event, Elon Musk, Chief Executive Officer of Tesla, introduced innovations in autonomous driving, while Dr. Sophia Keller, a robotics engineer at ETH Zurich, discussed AI-driven safety mechanisms. In parallel, Mehul Choudhary, Policy Head at the Reserve Bank of India, issued a statement from Mumbai, addressing the regulatory approach toward cryptocurrency adoption.\r\n\r\nLater, on June 25, 2022, Professor William Harris of Harvard Business School convened a workshop in Boston with participants including Sarah Ahmed, Chief Risk Officer at Deutsche Bank, and Carlos Fernandez, Compliance Director at Banco Santander. They debated the role of ethics in machine learning algorithms applied to financial credit scoring. Concluding the event, Nidhi Kapoor, Lead Researcher at United Nations Economic and Social Council, released a paper outlining global standards for responsible AI deployment in the finance sector.",{"entities":[[3,19,"DATE"],[21,37,"NAMES"],[39,59,"OCC"],[63,95,"ORG"],[122,131,"LOC"],[213,227,"NAMES"],[229,245,"OCC"],[253,263,"ORG"],[392,401,"OCC"],[402,413,"NAMES"],[417,443,"ORG"],[483,497,"LOC"],[502,510,"LOC"],[539,550,"NAMES"],[552,574,"OCC"],[578,593,"ORG"],[682,698,"DATE"],[700,709,"NAMES"],[711,725,"OCC"],[733,755,"ORG"],[765,774,"LOC"],[788,804,"NAMES"],[806,814,"OCC"],[822,836,"ORG"],[972,989,"NAMES"],[993,1012,"OCC"],[1016,1035,"ORG"],[1039,1044,"LOC"],[1106,1112,"DATE"],[1127,1138,"NAMES"],[1140,1159,"OCC"],[1163,1173,"ORG"],[1196,1211,"OCC"],[1217,1230,"ORG"],[1235,1249,"ORG"],[1300,1314,"DATE"],[1319,1332,"LOC"],[1334,1348,"NAMES"],[1350,1365,"OCC"],[1369,1392,"ORG"],[1406,1419,"NAMES"],[1421,1444,"OCC"],[1448,1469,"ORG"],[1495,1520,"ORG"],[1545,1562,"NAMES"],[1566,1587,"OCC"],[1591,1628,"ORG"],[1683,1692,"LOC"],[1694,1705,"NAMES"],[1707,1725,"OCC"],[1729,1754,"ORG"],[1767,1772,"OCC"],[1824,1837,"DATE"],[1839,1850,"NAMES"],[1852,1877,"OCC"],[1881,1897,"ORG"],[1922,1931,"LOC"],[1942,1954,"NAMES"],[1956,1973,"OCC"],[1977,1986,"ORG"],[1992,2005,"NAMES"],[2007,2030,"OCC"],[2034,2054,"ORG"],[2180,2194,"NAMES"],[2221,2241,"ORG"],[2299,2311,"LOC"],[2318,2330,"DATE"],[2332,2342,"NAMES"],[2344,2368,"OCC"],[2373,2381,"ORG"],[2407,2420,"LOC"],[2456,2466,"ORG"],[2481,2490,"NAMES"],[2492,2515,"OCC"],[2519,2524,"ORG"],[2578,2595,"NAMES"],[2599,2616,"OCC"],[2620,2630,"ORG"],[2684,2699,"NAMES"],[2701,2712,"OCC"],[2720,2741,"ORG"],[2767,2773,"LOC"],[2855,2868,"DATE"],[2870,2879,"OCC"],[2880,2894,"NAMES"],[2898,2921,"ORG"],[2945,2951,"LOC"],[2957,2969,"OCC"],[2980,2991,"NAMES"],[2993,3011,"OCC"],[3015,3028,"ORG"],[3034,3050,"NAMES"],[3052,3071,"OCC"],[3075,3091,"ORG"],[3214,3226,"NAMES"],[3228,3243,"OCC"],[3247,3289,"ORG"]]}]]}