{"classes":["ORG","DATE","PRODUCTS","LOCATION","AMT","PERSON"],"annotations":[["In Q1 2024, Microsoft reported revenue of 20.1 billion U.S. dollars. CEO Satya Nadella highlighted strong demand for Azure cloud services in North America.  \r",{"entities":[[3,10,"DATE"],[12,21,"ORG"],[42,68,"AMT"],[73,86,"PERSON"],[117,137,"PRODUCTS"],[141,154,"LOCATION"]]}],["Apple shipped 60 million iPhones in Asia during Q1 2024, earning 25.3 billion U.S. dollars. Tim Cook noted that innovation in the M3 chip boosted performance. \r",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"],[14,32,"PRODUCTS"],[36,40,"LOCATION"],[48,55,"DATE"],[65,91,"AMT"],[92,100,"PERSON"]]}],["Samsung recorded 72 million smartphone shipments in Europe in Q2 2023, generating 21.4 billion U.S. dollars. President TM Roh emphasized the success of the Galaxy S23 series. \r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ORG"],[17,38,"PRODUCTS"],[52,58,"LOCATION"],[62,69,"DATE"],[82,108,"AMT"],[119,125,"PERSON"],[156,173,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["Dell posted revenue of 12.4 billion U.S. dollars in Q2 2023 from laptop sales in North America. Michael Dell said enterprise demand for Latitude models remained solid. \r",{"entities":[[0,4,"ORG"],[23,48,"AMT"],[52,59,"DATE"],[65,71,"PRODUCTS"],[81,95,"LOCATION"],[96,108,"PERSON"]]}],["Tesla achieved revenue of 24.2 billion U.S. dollars in Q2 2023, driven by strong Model Y sales in the United States. Elon Musk announced plans to expand production in Texas.  \r",{"entities":[[0,5,"ORG"],[26,43,"AMT"],[55,62,"DATE"],[81,88,"PRODUCTS"],[102,116,"LOCATION"],[117,126,"PERSON"]]}],["",{"entities":[]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}