{"classes":["ORG","DATE","MONEY","INDEX","PER","PRODUCT","GPE"],"annotations":[["Microsoft Corporation announced its quarterly earnings on July 18, 2024, reporting a revenue of $56.2 billion.\r",{"entities":[[0,21,"ORG"],[58,71,"DATE"],[96,109,"MONEY"]]}],null,["On March 5, 2023, Amazon introduced a new subscription plan priced at $9.99 per month.\r",{"entities":[[3,16,"DATE"],[18,24,"ORG"],[70,75,"MONEY"]]}],null,["Goldman Sachs projected that the S&P 500 index would rise by 8% during the fiscal year 2025.\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"ORG"],[61,63,"PER"],[87,91,"DATE"]]}],null,["Google unveiled its new AI chip called Tensor X3 at the Cloud Next conference in San Francisco.\r",{"entities":[[0,6,"ORG"],[39,48,"PRODUCT"],[81,94,"GPE"]]}],null,["On December 12, 2022, Netflix signed a multi-year content deal worth $500 million with a Hollywood studio.\r",{"entities":[[3,20,"DATE"],[22,29,"ORG"],[69,81,"MONEY"],[89,105,"ORG"]]}],null,["Apple Inc. reported a net income of $22.9 billion for the quarter ending September 2024.\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"ORG"],[36,49,"MONEY"],[73,87,"DATE"]]}],null,["Tesla Inc., trading under ticker TSLA, announced plans to build a new Gigafactory in Mexico by mid-2025.\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"ORG"],[95,103,"DATE"]]}],null,["JPMorgan Chase revised its forecast for the euro-dollar exchange rate for Q1 2025.\r",{"entities":[[0,14,"ORG"],[74,81,"DATE"]]}],null,["On August 2, 2023, Meta Platforms launched its Threads application to rival Twitter.\r",{"entities":[[3,17,"DATE"],[19,23,"ORG"],[47,54,"PRODUCT"],[76,83,"ORG"]]}],null,["Intel Corporation invested $20 billion in a semiconductor plant located in Ohio.",{"entities":[[0,17,"ORG"],[27,38,"MONEY"],[75,79,"GPE"]]}]]}